我和我的哥哥们是历史上
最早的吸血鬼
REBEKAH: My brothers and I
are the first vampires in history.
是真祖家族
The Originals.
三百年前，我们把纽奥良当作家
Three hundred years ago,
we called New Orleans home.
在这里，曾经有一段时间，我很快乐
I was happy here...
for a time.
现在我们重回这里，发现了一个奇迹
Now, we've returned,
only to find a miracle.
尼克劳斯，她怀了你的孩子
Niklaus, the girl is carrying
your child.
随之，就有了新的责任
REBEKAH: And with it,
a new responsibility.
我会一直保护你
I will always protect you.
我向你保证
You have my word on that.
但我们家族有很多敌人
REBEKAH: But our family
has many enemies.
克劳斯毁了我生命中所有美好的事情
Klaus destroyed
everything good in my life.
所以我就要夺走他最想要的东西
So, I'm gonna take away
the thing he wants most.
这些威胁本应该让我们团结起来
REBEKAH: These threats
should have united us.
然而，克劳斯却让我们分裂
Instead, Klaus has driven us apart.
你这么对以利亚，我为什么要帮你？
Why should I help you
after what you did to Elijah?
你是我的家人
You're my family.
克劳斯永远不会停止控制你
Klaus will never stop
trying to control you.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
我哥哥以为我忠心于他
REBEKAH:
My brother expects my loyalty,
一如既往，但现在，也许
as he has for 1,000 years,
but now, perhaps,
是时候做出另一种选择了
it's time to make a different choice.
我不该再回到这里的
REBEKAH: I should never
have come back here.
我在这里坠入爱河
This is the town
where I fell in love...
却被爱情所伤
...and where love failed us.
我想你知道我在说谁
I assume you know
who I'm talking about.
你应该知道，我和马赛尔
You should know, Marcel and l
现在关系不是很好
are not on the best of terms
right now.
但你是一个神父，难道你不该
REBEKAH: But you are
an active priest, are you not?
准备好倾听我的忏悔吗？
Ready and able to hear
my confession?
通常“愿意”这个词
Usually, the word "willing"
应该会出现在这个句子中
falls somewhere in that sentence.
你是天主教徒吗？
Are you even Catholic?
我已经在这个世界活了一千年了
I've been on this earth
for 1,000 years.
我不敢肯定地说我相信上帝之类的
I can't say for certain that
I believe in anything like a God,
但我需要有人
but I need absolution...
来赦免我的罪
...from someone, anyone.
所以你愿不愿意听我的忏悔呢？
So will you hear my confession
or not?
神父，请宽恕我的罪
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
我是一个骗子，叛徒
I am a liar, a betrayer.
我密谋对付我的亲人
I have conspired
against my own blood.
我甚至怀疑你的上帝能不能拯救我
And I doubt even your God
could save me.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：逆流之河
(24小时前）
主演：约瑟夫摩根
你今天跟我们的好朋友
马赛尔聊过了吗？
Have you spoken to our
good friend Marcel today?
没有，我该找他聊吗？
No. Should I have?
他最近一直悄无声息
Well, he's been
mysteriously silent,
神秘地躲着我
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
avoiding me, some might say.
我想也许他低声地对着你的耳朵
主演：克莱儿荷特
I thought, perhaps,
he may have whispered
把原因告诉了你
主演：克莱儿荷特
reasons into your ear...
在他跟你甜言蜜语时
主演：菲比托金
...along with all of those
sweet nothings.
如果我看到他，我一定会问问
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
If I see him,
I'll be sure to ask
他是不是还在生你的气
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
if he's still sore at you.
我帮你那个眼神配个音吧
Let me give a voice
to that look in your eyes.
我圣洁高尚的哥哥在河口
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
"My saintly, noble brother lies
痛苦地打滚
writhing in agony in the bayou,
被混蛋的哥哥咬了一口
主演：莉雅派普斯
victim of my bastard
brother's bite
只要一两滴他的血
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
when just one or two drops
就能舒缓他的疼痛
of his blood would
ease his pain."
恰恰相反，尼克
我只是在享用我的早餐
On the contrary, Nik.
I am simply enjoying my brekkie
等着以利亚恢复过来
waiting for Elijah's healthy return.
得了吧，蕾贝卡
Oh, come on, Rebekah.
整个早上你都用那种
恶狠狠的眼神瞪着我
You've been giving me
the devil's eye all morning.
说吧
Out with it.
也许我是在担心，如果我说出了
Perhaps, I'm concerned that
if I voice my opinion
你对以利亚干的事的看法，最终我会
about what you did to Elijah,
I will end up
被你的毒牙反咬一口
on the wrong side of
your toxic Hybrid teeth.
胡说，我绝对不会咬你
Poppycock.
I would never bite you.
以利亚在我对我孩子的意图这事上
Elijah made some very offensive
accusations
做出了非常无理的指控
about my intentions
towards my child.
他活该难受这么一两天
He deserves a day or two
of discomfort.
除此之外，你知道的
Besides,
you know my preferred method
处罚你们的轻率之举
of punishment
for your indiscretions
我更喜欢用匕首
is the dagger.
制片：兰斯安德森
你真的很有问题
There's something
fundamentally wrong with you.
来，把这喝了
Here. Drink this.
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
请原谅我
Forgive me, please.
没关系
It's okay.
记得提醒我，等你恢复了
Remind me to annihilate
your brother
就去灭了你弟弟
once you're healthy.
好，记得提醒我提醒你先排队
Yes. Remind me to remind you
to get in line.
我们躲在这种偏僻地方
编剧：戴克兰迪巴拉，茱莉普烈克
Doesn't help that we decided
to shack up
也不能去找他报仇
in the middle of a swamp, either.
导演：杰西瓦恩
- 你还好吗？
- 我没事
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
你继续去看书吧
Please just return to your reading.
我把整本都看了一遍
Well, I went through
the whole thing.
只是一本普通的圣经
It's just a regular Bible.
记录了一个家族族谱
With an entry in the family tree
不知道是否和我有关
that may or may not be me,
但你知道我一直都很担心你
but you know I've been
a little busy worrying about you.
海莉，拜托
Hayley, please.
这高烧会让我变得情绪不稳
This fever will make me unstable.
一旦这些幻觉出现
Now,
once these hallucinations begin,
我就会看到一些东西
I'll start to see things.
会开始胡言乱语
I will start to say things.
让我一个人静静吧
You must leave me here.
我不能就这样把你留在这里
I'm not leaving you like this.
好了，我来了，开始吧
All right. I'm here.
Let's do this.
我会说得简单点
I'll keep this simple.
这孩子是你们最爱的克劳斯的一个宿敌
This kid is an old enemy of
your favorite person Klaus.
现在，他有许多话要说
Now, he's got plenty to say
关于那个不忠的混蚤
about what that traitorous
都瞒着我干了些什么
son of a bitch has been up to
behind my back.
现在，胆小想离开的
Now, for those of you
faint of heart...
门在那边
...there's the door.
因为一旦留下来
Because those who stick around,
就代表你们要加入战争
you're signing up for battle.
你们都知道克劳斯并不一直都是混合种
You all know Klaus wasn't
always the Hybrid.
当他打破抑制他狼人一面的诅咒时
When he broke the curse that
kept his werewolf side dormant,
这个过程中
somewhere in all that,
有一部分狼人血统压制了吸血鬼的一面
certain parts were now able
to trump his vampire side,
比如能够传递狼人的基因
Iike the ability to pass
on the werewolf gene.
这就牵扯到了他一直
藏着的那个狼人女孩
That's where the werewolf girl he's
been hiding from you all comes in.
她来到我生活的小镇，假装是我的朋友
She rolled through my town,
pretended to be my friend,
最后却勾搭上了他
and ended up
hooking up with him.
现在她怀着他的孩子
Now she's pregnant with his kid.
什么乱七八糟的？
What the hell is this?
听完再说
Just listen.
当克劳斯变成混合种时
When Klaus became the Hybrid...
他找到了办法，让纯种的狼人
...he figured out a way
to turn full-bred werewolves
变成像他一样的生物
into creatures like him.
我就是
You're looking at one of them.
好处是，我们拥有作为吸血鬼的优势
On the plus side,
we had all the perks of being vampires.
我们更强大，速度更快
We were stronger, faster,
我们咬人时分泌的毒素还能杀死吸血鬼
and the toxins in our bites
could still kill a vampire,
但坏处就是，我们效忠于他
but on the downside,
we were loyal to him.
超自然地效忠
Like, supernaturally loyal.
是吗？但你却在这里说出了他的秘密
Right, and that's why you're
here spilling all his secrets?
不，这就是重点，迪亚哥
No, that's the point, Diego.
他找到了打破效忠的办法
He figured out a way to break
free of it.
我也帮助了其他人
And I helped
the rest of them, too.
然后克劳斯因为他们的背叛杀了他们
Then Klaus killed them
for their betrayal.
因为那就是克劳斯的作风
Because that is what Klaus does.
别介意
我只是被这故事吸引了
Don't mind me.
I'm fascinated by this story.
- 你好，泰勒
- 蕾贝卡
-Hello, Tyler.
-Rebekah.
好久不见
Long time, no see.
秦勒想说的是
What Tyler is about to tell you
我哥哥可以利用他孩子的血
is that my brother can use
his baby's blood
制造更多混合种
to sire more Hybrids.
你们会发现吸血鬼到时
就毫无立足之地了
What you will all figure out
is that vampires don't stand a chance.
秦勒，我猜你是想让
所有吸血鬼联合起来
So, Tyler, I assume you were
trying to rally this lot
确保这个孩子不会出生
into making sure
the baby isn't born.
是的
Yeah.
你不喜欢的话，尽管去帮你哥哥吧
You don't like it, go ahead
and take your brother's side,
但你知道我说得没错
but you know I'm right.
我想你误会了这位女士的意图
I believe you've mistaken
the lady's intentions.
好吧，到底怎么回事？
All right.
What's going on?
你做得很对，秦勒
You're absolutely right, Tyler.
我哥哥这个人简直糟糕透了
My brother is a crap enough
individual as it is.
绝不能再让他制造一群更优越的物种
The last thing he needs is
to sire a superior species.
说啊，告诉他们
Go on. You can tell them.
她不是来对付我们的
She's not here to fight us.
她是来帮我们的
She's here to help us.
没错，但首先…
That's right, but first...
呼…
Whew...
伤害那孩子的话题就说到这吧
That is enough talk
about harming that baby.
克劳斯才是我们要阻止的人
Klaus is the one
we're putting a stop to.
他们都抛弃了我
KLAUS:
They have all forsaken me.
我的兄弟姊妹和我父母一样
My siblings are as deceitful
and diseased
虚伪，病态
as my parents ever were.
指责我为了一己之私利用自己的孩子
Accusing me of using
my baby for my own gain.
比起自己的家人更信任外人
Trusting others
before their own blood.
给我台笔电不行吗？
Would a laptop kill you?
海明威很喜欢那台打字机
That typewriter was good
enough for Hemingway.
你们的确有相似之处
I can see the resemblance.
酗酒和胡乱施暴
Booze and random acts of violence.
以利亚和蕾贝卡用他们恶毒的谎言
Elijah and Rebekah
have cut to the quick
深深伤害了我
with their vicious lies about me
我所做的一切都是为了赢得
when all I've done is tried to win
这场战争，从马赛尔的手中夺回
this battle of wills over
Marcel's control
法语区的控制权，拿回我们的家
of the Quarter
in order to reclaim our home.
继续打啊
Type, please.
有什么意义呢？
What's the point?
你只不过是一遍遍重复说着同样的事
You just repeat the same thing
over and over again.
蕾贝卡要弄垮你，以利亚要弄垮你
Rebekah is out to get you.
Elijah is out to get you.
有没有人不想把你弄垮呢？
Is there anyone
who isn't plotting your downfall?
我怀疑你连自己的影子都不相信
I doubt you trust
your own reflection.
如果匕首没有失踪
You know,
if the daggers weren't missing,
我一定会在他们的胸口各插一把
I would put one
in each of their hearts.
让他们停歇几个世纪，我也好耳根清净
Rid myself of the burden of my
siblings for a couple of centuries.
瞧瞧你
Look at you,
一次又一次重复着同样消极的循环
repeating the same destructive cycles
over and over again.
是你自己造就了你的不幸
You are the architect
of your own unhappiness.
我不记得我征询过你的建议
I don't remember asking
for your advice.
是吗？
Oh, really?
纽奥良那么多人
So, of all the people
in New Orleans,
你却选了一个有心理学硕士学位的人
you choose someone
with a master's in psychology
记录你的传记
你都一千多岁了
to record your life story.
You're over a thousand years old.
绝对知道怎么打字
Pretty damn sure
you know how to type.
真相就是，你魅惑我来这里
The truth is,
you compel me to come here
因为你没有其他人可倾诉
because you have no one else
to talk to,
而你想要被理解
and you want to be understood.
然后你魅惑我，一离开这里
Then you compel me
to forget everything
就忘记一切
因为你太害怕，不敢信任任何人
as soon as I leave your presence
because you're too scared to trust.
我什么都不怕
I am scared of nothing.
这是什么？
What is this?
这是个古老的神秘图案
我要用它摧毁你
It's an ancient, mystical plot
I'm using to destroy you.
别紧张，这只是个纹身设计图
Relax. It's a tattoo design.
空闲时间再画这些
Draw on your own time.
这就是我的空闲时间
你强占了我的时间
This is my time.
You steal it from me.
你想把他放在哪？
Where do you want him?
随便放在什么方便的地方
Well, just put him anywhere handy
直到处理完克劳斯
until Klaus is taken care of.
我们要把克劳斯放在哪？
Where are we gonna put Klaus?
他得和其他人离得远远的
He needs to be away
from all the others.
我们可不希望他挑起战争
We don't want him
fomenting dissent.
你知道他很善于运用言语
他能用嘴皮解决一切
You know he has a knack with words.
He could talk his way out of hell.
没错，我在后面为他挑了一块地方
Yeah. I got a spot picked
out for him in the back.
接下来的52年里
他只能和他自己说话了
Only person he's gonna be talking to
for the next 52 years is himself.
52年？
Fifty-two?
他在19世纪时用匕首封了你52年
One for each year that he kept
you daggered in the 1800s.
当时你默许他用匕首封住我
You mean,
you let him keep me daggered.
克劳斯关在这里的每一年
我都会向你道歉
And I'll spend every year Klaus is
in here apologizing to you for it.
随便几年就够了
Well, I'll settle for long enough
只要我能享受到一点真正的快乐
to experience just
a little bit of happiness...
并确保我的侄女不会变成
混合种繁殖机器
...and ensure that my niece isn't turned
into a Hybrid breeding machine.
要把他关在这里很困难
It's gonna be tough to keep him
in here.
你的那个小女巫
能够增加我们的胜算
That little witch of yours
would put the odds in our favor.
我不能冒险
I can't risk it.
她最近越来越不能控制她的魔法了
She's got less and less control
over her magic lately.
我根本没法让她离开教堂阁楼
I can't even get her out
of the church attic,
更不可能指望她去对付克劳斯
much less rely on her to go
to battle against Klaus.
那我们就需要你派出最好的战士
Then we'll need
your very best warriors.
克劳斯很强大，也很狡猾
Klaus is strong and crafty,
背叛会让他特别生气
and betrayal makes him
particularly nasty.
我们所做的事，每一件
What we're doing is nothing Klaus
克劳斯都对你和你哥哥
hasn't done to both
you and your brother
做过很多次
a dozen times over.
你不是在动摇吧？
You're not getting second
thoughts now, are you?
没有，没有动摇
No.
These aren't second thoughts.
只是很后悔
They're feelings of regret.
一百年前我就应该埋了他
I should've buried him
a hundred years ago.
这样我们就可以多在一起一百年
It's a hundred years
we could've been together.
没事的，没事
It's okay. It's okay.
莎莉丝特
ELlJAH: Celeste.
哦，莎莉丝特
Oh, Celeste.
海莉，对不起
Hayley, I'm sorry.
我把你当成别人了
I thought you were someone else.
- 莎莉丝特？
- 对
-Celeste?
-Yes.
不管她是谁，她确实非常性感
Whoever she was,
she was smoking hot.
你怎么…
How....
我让你进入我的脑袋了吗？
Did I let you enter my thoughts?
我感觉不太好，我该走了
I'm not well.
I should go.
- 这…
- 没事的
-This is....
-This is fine.
以利亚，你病了，我在照顾你
Elijah, you're sick.
I'm taking care of you.
我们被监视了
We're being watched.
嘿！
Hey!
老天，我永远也习惯不了你这样出现
Oh, man,
I'll never get used to that.
我怎么感觉你学过戏剧呢？
Why do I get the feeling
you studied theater?
整个世界就是一个舞台，约书亚
All the world's a stage,
young Joshua,
而我恰巧是你终生难忘的角色
and it just so happens I have
the role of a lifetime for you.
你有什么消息，小约？
What do you got, Josh?
我有什么消息？
What do I got?
克劳斯要我从你这偷一把什么匕首
Klaus wants me to steal
some dagger from you.
这是试探
It's a test, okay?
他一定知道我为你效力，我确定
He knows I'm working for you.
I'm sure of it.
那个混蛋又想用匕首封住我们了
That bastard
wants to dagger us again.
他的下场都是他自找的
He deserves everything
he's gonna get.
别紧张
Relax.
如果他知道了
你现在早就被撕成两半了
If he knew, he would've ripped your
spine out through your nose by now.
好极了
Oh, great.
我现在真是超轻松的
我该怎么做？
Now I feel totally at ease.
What am I supposed to do?
你告诉他，你到处都找过了
You tell him
you searched high and low
就是找不到匕首
but you couldn't find the dagger.
天啊，我死定了
Oh, God, I'm so dead.
然后你告诉他，你看到我拿着
Then you tell him you saw
I had it on me,
如果他想要，他就得自己来拿
that if he wants it,
he'll have to come and get it,
这可不容易，因为我很多疑
which won't be easy
because I'm paranoid
还加强了防卫
and I beefed up my posse.
是这样，我不是在怀疑
All right.
So, not doubting
你身为吸血鬼的毁灭能力
your mad vampire skills of
destruction or anything,
但马赛尔现在高度戒备
but Marcel is on red alert,
派了很多人保护他
surrounded by, like, an army.
你会被粉身碎骨的，除非…
You're totally boned unless....
除非什么？
Unless what?
我听到他和迪亚哥争吵
I overheard him arguing
with Diego.
显然他今晚会清理场地
Apparently, he's clearing out
the compound tonight
为了一个约会什么的
for a date or something.
总之他会在那里
That's where Marcel will be.
待我统治纽奥良时
When I run New Orleans,
我会为你率备一枚永恒的日光戒指
约书亚
there will be a permanent
daylight ring in it for you, Joshua,
作为你效忠真正国王的赏赐
for services rendered
unto your true king.
好极了
Cool.
但你若胆敢背叛我
But if you ever betray me...
我会确保你无尽的余生
I will make sure you spend
the rest of your eternal life
将在极端的苦痛中度过
乞求以死解脱
in exquisite agony
wishing for a merciful death.
永别了，克劳斯
Adios, Klaus.
你想怎么样？
What do you want?
这是爱尔兰蒸馏酒
It's Poitin.
传说此酒能让死者复活
It'd raise the dead,
杀了他们，再把他们复活
kill them, and raise them again.
我想跟你谈谈你侄女卡蜜儿的事
I'd like to talk to you
about your niece, Camille.
相信你也早有怀疑
I'm sure you suspect this already
根据她记忆里的空隙不难推断
by the gaps in her memory.
我魅惑了她
I compel her.
起初是因为她是个有用的间谋
At first, it was because
she was a useful spy
但如今是为了保护她
but now for her own protection.
我猜一定是有吸血鬼在扰乱她的心智
I assumed a vampire
was messing with her mind,
但我从没想过你会供认不讳
though I never anticipated
a confession.
她始终不肯放下往事
She won't leave things be.
这教堂内发生的惨剧
Her mind churns
with the permutations
她的双胞胎哥哥大开杀戒的画面
of what happened in this church
在她脑海中翻腾交织
when her twin went on
his slaughter spree.
眼下，如果她知道了事情的真相
Now, if she finds out
what really happened...
知道事关吸血鬼及女巫的诅咒
That the vampires and witch
hexes were involved...
她一定会不断追查下去
直到涉入过深
She will dig and dig and dig
until she digs too deep
最终因此丧命
and gets herself killed.
纽奥良将会成为她的葬身之地
New Orleans
will be the death of her.
她必须离开
She needs to leave...
而且虽说来讽刺
...and, as ironic as it may seem,
但我希望由她自己做出这个选择
I believe it should be her choice.
没错
Yes.
与控制人心智的吸血鬼
谈论自由意志的确很讽刺
It is ironic discussing free will
with a mind-controlling vampire.
她是个聪明的女孩
She's a clever girl.
她今早才教训了我一顿
She gave me a piece of
her mind earlier today.
换作其他人我早杀了
I would've killed others for less.
我在乎她的生死
I care about her survival.
我嗅到了战争的气息
I smell war in the air,
而每一场战争
and with every war,
都有无辜的受害者可避免战火的牵连
there is the innocent victim
who could have been spared
如果他们能及早逃开
if they had just walked away.
请说服她离开纽奥良
Please convince her to walk away
from New Orleans...
否则我不得不以魅惑逼她离开
...or I'll be forced
to compel her to go.
这位绅士，能帮我擦身吗？
Assistance, please, good sir.
不，我更乐意欣赏眼前的美景
No. I'm much happier taking
in such a wondrous view.
如此醉人的美景
It's perfection.
你那弟弟又不安分了
Your brother is again
up to no good.
他向贵族们发起决斗的挑战
He's challenging the gentry
to duels
好像他们能有公平竞争的机会似的
as though they have any
chance of a fair fight.
我已厌倦了牺牲我自身的愉悦
I do grow weary
of sacrificing my joy
去替我弟弟收拾残局
to temper my brother's mischief.
你一定能施个咒吧
Surely, you can cast a spell.
让他不能胡作非为
Put him in his place.
那得上百个女巫才能办到了
It will take 100 witches
to put him in his place.
再说，他向来只听你的话
Besides,
he only ever listens to you.
这倒是
Yes.
他真的要学会点规矩了
He certainly needs
a little discipline.
也许打屁股是个好办法
Perhaps a spanking of
some kind is in order.
我想我需要先练习一下，来
I think I shall need some rehearsal.
Come.
海莉，拜托，这场高烧
Hayley, please.
This fever.
让我的脑海中充斥着痛苦的回忆
My mind is flooded with
these tortuous memories.
你必须离开
You have to leave.
你这人怎么回事？
What is your deal?
你不喜欢被人照顾吗？
You don't like people taking
care of you?
关心我的人都没好下场
There are consequences for those
that care.
我不会让你承受这些的
I will not have you pay that price.
你不就做了些奇怪的复古春梦吗？
So you're having weird
retro sex dreams.
别多想了，我是留定了
Get over it. I'm staying.
之前的那个访客呢？
So, what about our visitor?
她想干什么？
What does she want?
我猜昨晚在门口留下这本
I'm guessing she's the one that
神秘圣经的人就是她
Ieft the mystery Bible on
the doorstep last night.
要是她愿意多留一会
Would be nice
if she'd stick around
告诉我个中缘由就好了
Iong enough to tell me why.
海莉，你是来寻找你家人的线索的
Hayley, you came here to gather
information about your family,
不是来照顾一个发高烧的吸血鬼
not to play nursemaid to
a vampire with a temperature.
拜托，去找她
问出你想知道的一切
Please... find her.
Learn what you can.
不，我要留下来
No. I'm staying.
克劳斯
Klaus.
你一直没接我的电话
You've been avoiding my calls.
我最近有点生气
A little pissed off lately.
我稍后再为我的所作所为道歉
Apologies for my behavior
can come later.
你手上有我的东西，还给我
You have something of mine.
I want it back.
抱歉，我不能还你
Sorry, but I can't do that.
这是什么意思？
What is this?
为你的所作所为道歉？
Apologies for your behavior?
你不会道歉的，尼克，你只会装一下
You don't apologize, Nik.
You just act.
我受够了，我们都受够了
I've had enough.
We have had enough.
瞧瞧，你终于将唯一能
Well, look at you,
finally in possession
让你陷入沉睡的武器拿到手了
of the one thing
that can take you down.
- 感觉如何？
- 好极了
-How does it feel?
-Great.
就这样吗？
So this is it.
禽兽克劳斯的行为已经人神共愤
The evil bastard Klaus
has gone too far,
必须受到惩罚
must be punished.
而且还是由他的妹妹来执行
And by his own sibling,
nonetheless.
跟圣经真有异曲同工之妙
How positively biblical.
至于你，马赛尔
And you, Marcel,
这就是你所谓的致命一击吗？
is this your idea of a hit?
我教你的围剿可不止
靠这样一群乌合之众
I taught you better than this
paltry excuse for a takedown.
你以为这样就能制服我吗？
You think you can subdue me
with this?
是不能，但或许这样就足够了
No, but I think I can with this.
嗯
Well....
莎莉丝特
Celeste....
原谅我
Forgive me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
就这样吗？
Is that it?
这就是纽奥良最强的枪手？
Is this the best New Orleans
has to offer?
弟弟，住手吧，这太荒唐了
Brother, please.
This is high folly.
难道你这几周来
Is it not enough
that you have slaughtered
杀戮得还不够吗？
dozens in just these past
several weeks?
这个嘛…
Well....
城里横尸遍地的消息
很快就会传到大洋彼岸
Word of a city littered with bodies
will surely travel the oceans.
你想把父亲引来吗？
Do you want to bring our father
upon us?
别担心，哥哥
Relax, brother.
我已经放出风声说这些尸体
I've sent rumor that
the bodies are a result
是女巫为了寻找血祭的祭品而造成的
of the witches seeking blood
sacrifice for their rituals.
你做了什么？
You did what?
难道你忘了莎莉丝特正是
Have you forgotten
Celeste is one of those
你嫁祸对象的其中一人吗？
that you so recklessly
pointed your finger at?
谁是莎莉丝特？
Who's Celeste?
对了，就是最近跟你鬼混的女巫是吧？
Oh, yes, the witch
you've been knocking around with.
别担心
妓女在法语区就如老鼠一样
Well, fear not.
Harlots are like rats in the Quarter.
每走一步都能踩到一只
You trip over one
every step you take.
你在乎她，那真是不幸
You care about her.
Well, that is unfortunate.
我听说他们现在正在抓捕全城的女巫
I hear they're rounding up
the town's witches as we speak.
以利亚？
Elijah?
尼克劳斯，我要杀了你这个混蛋
Niklaus, I'll kill you,
you bastard.
以利亚？
Elijah?
我也很高兴认识你
Hello to you, too.
我们结束这幼稚的游戏吧
Let's end this charade, shall we?
纽奥良的吸血鬼们
Vampires of New Orleans...
要记住我是真祖之一我是混合种
...do recall that I am an Original,
a Hybrid.
我有不死之身
I cannot be killed.
永恒是一段很长的时间
Eternity is an awfully long time.
你们觉得马赛尔还能掌权多久？
How long to you think
Marcel will stay in power?
如果你们其中一人愿意放了我
What if one of you lot
were to release me,
将会得到我永恒的感恩
knowing I would be eternally
in your debt?
我会可怜那些敢与我对抗的人
I would pity those of you
who dared to cross me.
我向你们保证
I can assure you...
你们一定会死得轰轰烈烈
...your ends would be spectacular.
这是我从一个老朋友那
To borrow a trick...
学来的把戏
...from an old friend....
谁捡起这枚硬币
Whoever picks up this coin...
就能活下去
...gets to live.
现在，你们这群混蛋
有人要加入我吗？
Now, which of you magnificent
bastards wants to join me?
想要那枚硬币的人
Anyone wants that coin,
向克劳斯宣誓效忠吧
pledge allegiance to Klaus.
就是现在
Take it now.
去吧，选择权在你们手上
Go ahead.
The choice is yours.
拿下他
Take him.
马赛尔，过来我们决一死战！
Marcel! Come and finish this!
不要去
No.
- 捡起硬币
- 你说什么？
-Take the coin.
-What?
不杀光所有人他是不会罢休的
他也会杀了你
He won't stop until everyone is dead,
and he will kill you, too.
结束这一切吧，捡起硬币
End this. Pick up the coin.
够了
Enough!
瞧瞧啊
Well, well, well.
伟大的马赛尔
The great Marcel,
自称纽奥良国王的人
self-proclaimed king
of New Orleans,
正跪在我的面前
bowing before me.
拿去
There.
我在此宣誓效忠于你
I hereby pledge my allegiance
to you.
你现在拥有我的王国
You have the keys to my kingdom.
它是你的了
It's yours.
我正准备回家
I was on my way home,
看你偷偷溜了进来
saw you duck in here...
我就知道你一定会在这里
...knew exactly where you'd be.
这些恶作剧又来了
This is getting old.
这周第二次了
It's the second time this week.
是第三次
Third.
我前天才清理过
I cleaned it off
the day before yesterday.
一点用都没有，他们还会这么做的
It's pointless.
They'll just do it again.
大家只是需要时间来淡忘
Folks need time to heal.
西恩杀了许多无辜的人
Sean killed innocent people.
没人能这么快摆脱阴影
No one is getting over that
any time soon.
我觉得…
I think...
我觉得我要跟他一样发疯了
I think I'm losing it like he did.
我在口袋里发现了这个
I found this in my pocket.
这图案
The lines,
是我跟西恩小时候
经常用的暗号
it's a secret code Sean and l
used to use when we were kids.
但我不记得自己画过
I have no memory of drawing it.
有点不对劲，我也搞不清楚
Something is not right.
I just can't figure it out.
过来
Come here.
不如你离开这里一段时间吧
Maybe you should leave town
for a while.
出去散散心，放松一下
Give your head some space.
我认识你的系主任
I know your dean.
你可以先不急着写论文
You could put your thesis on hold.
不行
I can't.
这一定意味着什么
This means something.
我只是不知道
I just don't know what.
并不是每件事都要有意义
Not everything has meaning.
有时你要学会放下
Sometimes you just have to let go.
你应该离开纽奥良
You should leave New Orleans.
不是所有人都适合这里
This town isn't for everybody.
拜托
Please.
你一定有很多疑问
I'm sure you got questions.
大概有一箩筐吧
比如你是谁？
Only a thousand of them.
Like who are you?
你跟踪我干什么？
Why are you following me?
其他人都去哪里了？
Where the hell is everyone?
如果这本书里的人
And if the people in this book
真的是我的家人，他们出了什么事？
really are my family,
what happened to them?
我叫伊芙
I'm Eve.
我跟踪你是因为你让一个真祖吸血鬼
I'm following you
because you brought an Original
来到狼人的地盘
to werewolf country,
所以大多数狼人
which is pretty much
the same reason
都逃走了
why everybody else skedaddled.
如果你想知道
And if you want to know
what happened
族谱上的人出了什么事
to the people in that family tree,
简而言之
summing it up nice and quick,
是因为马赛尔
Marcel happened.
他做了什么？
What did he do?
大部分狼人都被他杀了
He killed most of them.
后来那些幸存下来的后代
Later, the descendents of the ones
who dodged death,
他迫使一个女巫对他们下了诅咒
he strong-armed a witch
into putting a curse on them.
什么样的诅咒？
What kind of curse?
那个诅咒颠覆了自然规律
Swap nature around, inside out,
使狼形成为他们的自然状态
made it so their natural state
was wolves.
只有在满月时才能变回人形
They only turn back human
on the full moon.
我们因为身上的印记而遭到追捕
就是那个新月胎记
We get hunted by the marks we carry,
that crescent moon birthmark.
所以我毁掉了自己的
That's why I got rid of mine.
我不想被人发现
I didn't want to get found out.
晚安
ELlJAH: Good evening.
我似乎…
Think I might have
不小心拿了你的东西
something which belongs to you.
以利亚，我来处理
你还好吗？
Elijah, I've got this.
Are you okay?
伤口愈合了，烧也退了
The wound had healed,
the fever has broken,
但奇怪的是
but for some strange reason...
我背上一直有股刺痛感
...I have this sharp and lingering
sensation in my back.
我得送他回家
但我会回来的，好吗？
I have to get him home,
but I'll be back, okay?
我想知道更多事
I need to know more.
遮好你的印记
Keep that mark covered up.
发生什么事了？
What happened?
我刚见到了我的家人
I just met part of my family.
看看你干的好事
Looking at what you've wrought?
听着，你要是想杀我
Look. If you're gonna kill me,
就速战速决吧
Iet's get this over with.
我为什么要杀你？
Why would I kill you?
你捡起了硬币
You picked up the coin.
战争也是有规则的，马赛尔
There are rules of engagement
in battle, Marcel.
没有规则，将是一片混乱
Without them,
you'd have anarchy.
而我倒想聊聊
I would, however, like to talk
所有权的问题
about accommodations.
比如你现在生活的区域
Your living quarters,
for example.
曾经是属于我的
I believe they used to be mine.
你想要这一切吗？可以，给你了
You want all this? Fine.
It's yours.
你可以把我赶回街上，无所谓
You can put me back
on the street for all I care.
不过有件事最好说清楚
But let's make one thing clear.
你永远无法拥有…
You'll never have this...
忠诚
Loyalty.
买不到，也无法拥有
You can't buy it.
You can't own it.
这是强求不来的
You can't force it.
忠诚只来自于对那些信任你的人
的爱和尊重
It comes only out of love
and respect
for the people who believe in you.
你教过我很多东西，尼克劳斯米卡森
You taught me many things,
Niklaus Mikaelson,
不过这个是我自己学到的
but this I learned myself...
而你永远无法领悟到这一点
...and it is something that
you will never know.
祝你统治愉快
Enjoy your kingdom.
谢谢你送我
So, thanks for the ride.
这一切有点尴尬，也有点惊险，是吧？
Quite the awkward, little adventure,
wouldn't you say?
抱歉我试图伤害你
我绝对不是故意的
I'm sorry I tried to hurt you.
I would never want that.
以利
Elij--
告诉我莎莉丝特怎么了
Tell me what happened
to Celeste.
- 这不重要
- 这很重要
-That's not important.
-lt is important.
你有一千年的记忆
A thousand years of memories,
你发烧出现幻觉时却只想到她？
and that's what breaks
through your fever brain?
我想知道，告诉我吧
I want to know.
Show me.
对女巫来说，那是个残忍而血腥的时代
It was a cruel and bloody time
to be a witch.
拜我那好弟弟所赐
Courtesy of my wonderful brother.
克劳斯杀了她吗？
She died because of Klaus?
是我害了她
She died because of me.
因为我太在乎她了
Because I cared too deeply for her.
我任由自己放松对克劳斯的管控
I had allowed my brother
to slip through my grasp.
而我自己却和莎莉丝特共享每一刻欢喻
I'd loosened the reins while
Celeste consumed my every moment.
我只顾自己享乐，放纵了他
I'd abandoned him in the
name of my own happiness.
莎莉丝特付出了生命的代价
Celeste paid the price.
我不懂
I don't get it.
我们为什么还回来？
Why are we here?
为什么你还要修补你们家族的关系？
Why are you trying to put
together your family
非常明显，它已经破裂了
when it's so clear that
one part of it is broken?
对我来说“破裂”
To me, the very definition
of the word "broken"
就表示那是可以修补的
suggests that
something can be fixed.
我有无尽的时间来完成这一个任务
I have all eternity
to accomplish one single task:
拯救我弟弟
my brother's salvation.
如果我放弃了，那么你告诉我
If I surrender this,
then, tell me,
我对我的家族，对我自己
对你腹中的孩子
what value would I be
to my family, to myself, to...
还有什么意义？
To your child?
不要这样，海莉
Please, no, Hayley.
你已经看到发生什么事了
You've seen what happens.
以利亚回来了，现在只有一把匕首
Elijah is home.
There's only one dagger.
今天你想惩罚我们中的哪个？
Which one of us will you
be punishing today?
我想到一个游戏
I contemplated a game
点兵点将，点到哪个就哪个
of eeny meeny minie moe.
你背叛了我，我的亲妹妹
You betrayed me, my own sister.
尼克劳斯，你敢
Niklaus, don't you dare.
那也许我该拿你开刀，哥哥
Well, perhaps it should be you,
brother,
对海莉温柔献媚，甜言蜜语
stealing my child away
with every fawning moment
然后就可以偷走我的孩子
of tenderness you show to Hayley.
这事跟海莉无关
This has nothing to do
with Hayley.
全都跟她有关！
It has everything to do with her!
她从刚来时就倾心于你
She's adored you
since she arrived.
现在我的孩子，我的亲生骨肉
And now my child, my blood,
长大后要叫你爸爸了
will grow up to call you father.
你是这么想的吗？
Is that what this is?
你又担心自己要被抛弃了吗？
You are once again worried
that you will be left behind?
这么多年你怎么还没明白？
不是我们抛弃你，尼克
Has history taught you nothing?
We don't abandon you, Nik.
是你一直弃我们不顾
You drive us away.
是这样吗？
Is that so?
我最近不是一直在配合你们吗？
What have I done lately
other than cooperate?
我向你低头，哥哥
I bowed down to you, brother...
为了弥补我桶了你
...to make up for daggering you,
为了我们要夺回家园的伟大计划
for the greater good of our plan
to reclaim our home.
相反地，妹妹
Look the other way, sister.
你又开始了和马赛尔的纠缠
While you repeat
the same cycle with Marcel,
又陷入这个你不该爱的男人的陷阱
falling again for a man
you shouldn't be with,
而他却统治着这个由我们建立起的帝国
while he controls the empire
that we built,
他占为己有
that he took!
对于我过去的罪恶，我无法否认
Now,
I make no excuses for past sins,
但那一刻，你们两个本可以
but in the one moment
when you two could have
选择支持我，相信我
chosen to stand by me.
To believe in me...
相信我对自己的亲骨肉没有别的意图
...and believe my intentions
for my own child were pure.
你们却选择背叛我
You chose to stand against me...
去和我的敌人站在一边
To side with my enemies.
我想夺回我们的家
I wanted our home back.
现在我成功了
Now I have it.
所以我要去那里生活
So, I'm going to live there.
你们两个
And the two of you...
就一起待在这里
You can stay here together...
慢慢腐烂吧
...and rot.
你跟我走，小狼
You're coming with me,
little wolf.
我干嘛要跟你走？
Why would I go anywhere with you?
海莉，因为你肚子里的孩子
Because, Hayley,
that child you carry
是这个世界上我唯一在乎的东西
is the only thing on this earth
that matters to me.
你可以反抗我，但你赢不了我
Now, you can fight me on this,
but you will lose.
任何想阻止你上车的人也赢不了我
As will anyone else who tries
to stop you getting in this car.
我弄明白了，我做的笔记
I figured it out, the note.
我一直在想，我的时间去哪了？
I was thinking about it--
my lost time,
为什么大脑一直昏昏沉沉的？
my foggy brain.
我以为我跟西恩一样疯了
I thought I must be going crazy
like Sean...
但后来我想，是不是我的潜意识里
...but then I thought,
"What if somewhere
in my subconscious,
想要给我自己暗示呢？
I was trying
to send myself a message?"
的确如此
I was.
（克劳斯 M
皮卡尤恩日报1919)
我在1919年的皮卡尤恩日报里
发现了这个
I found this in the Picayune
newspaper archives from 1919.
（皮卡尤恩日报）
看这张照片
Look at this photo.
这些人，我认识他们
Those men, I know them.
他们两个我都认识
I know both of them.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）